JASON R. DUFF

Charlotte, NC 28277 - 704 352 5777 - 2jduff@gmail.com http://jasonrduff.com

Professional Summary

Currently I am a Front-End Developer with 5+ years of experience developing websites for e-commerce clients. 11 years of self-employment selling, engineering, and installing residential audio and video equipment. 8+ years' experience as a project manager in the telecommunications industry overseeing up to 30 employees with multiple projects spread across North Carolina.

Work History

Front End Developer

MicroD - Charlotte, NC 2016 - Present

- Increase what I learned from an online boot camp and apply it to real world applications.
- Added knowledge of HTML, SCC, JQuery, Javascript and Angular to build web sites, landing pages, and projects.
- Used Figma to prototype designs for templated themes.
- Worked in a timely fashion to meet the demands of our clients with daily service tickets.
- Created e-commerce responsive websites for our customers.
- Built custom sites as well as templated sites for our e-commerce customers.

Owner

JD Audio - Charlotte, NC

2005 - 2016

- Utilized my communication, problem solving, technical, and organizational skills to keep my customer satisfaction at a high level.
- Won service awards every year since opening the business in 2005.
- Understanding how a business is run, and how to have a successful business.
- Managed multiple stressful jobs at the same time with the customer satisfaction in mind.

Project Manager

AccuNet Communications - Charlotte, NC

2000 - 2005

- Communicated with sales to approve engineering quotes and configuration of telecommunication systems.
- Delegated service requests, installation, and training to multiple levels of technicians.
- Provided performance, project, and budget reports to upper management.
- Located top quality vendors to stock warehouses for installation and service.
- Partnered with local telephone vendors to provide cost savings to customers.

Project Manager

Nextera / Williams Communications Solutions - Charlotte, NC

1997 - 2000

- Apply organizational skills to manage up to thirty technicians with service, installations, and training.
- Provide leadership to schedule and prioritize technicians' workloads with customers' needs in mind.
- Work closely with leaders of corporations on large projects to ensure their projects were on time with minimal down time.
- Created weekly budgetary reports, graphs, and presentations to upper management on all projects in North Carolina.
- Perform quartile presentations for the direct manager and general manager, which include customer satisfaction, technician productivity, and financial margins for the North Carolina region.

Technician

Wiltel / Williams Communications Solutions - Charlotte, NC

1994 - 1997

- Lead technician on assigned installation and service projects.
- Responsible for customer satisfaction at each site daily with minimal return visits.
- Worked with others as a team to complete large projects.
- Promoted to supervisor after six months.

Education

State of Florida College - Daytona Beach, FL
 Certificate in Electronic and Computer Technology

1990 - 1993